matterofcents.net 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Matter of Cents

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please [contact me here](mailto:bella0421@msn.com).

At Matter of Cents, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Matter of Cents and how it is used. **Log Files** Like many other Web sites, Matter of Cents makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons** Matter of Cents does not use cookies. **DoubleClick DART Cookie** .:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://matterofcents.net. .:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://matterofcents.net and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …. Google Adsense Commission Junction Clickbank Linkshare These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://matterofcents.blogspot.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs.

Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. http://matterofcents.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://matterofcents.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
